**Hello Everyone**

This is a Quiz Game CLI app which is the assignment for the NeoGcamp lesson 01. This is a game with 2 levels. As I am a beginner I have tried to put my best in it. This app is hosted on replit.com. Anyone can play this game by simply going to the link: https://replit.com/@SurajRai4/movie-quiz?embed=1&output=1#index.js

I am providing the answers for the questions in the game so that it would be easier to examine how the app is working and if the app is in obeying the code.

The questions are mentioned below:

 Level 1: Hollywood Movies

         1. question:"What are the dying words of Charles Foster Kane in Citizen Kane? ",
            answer:"Rosebud"
      

        2. question:"What 1927 musical was the first “talkie”? ",
           answer:"The Jazz Singer"

      
        3. question:"Who played Mrs. Robinson in The Graduate? ",
           answer:"Anne Bancroft",
      

        4. question:"What was the first feature-length animated movie ever released? ",
           answer:"Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
      

        5. question:"In The Matrix, does Neo take the blue pill or the red pill? ",
           answer:"Red"
      

 Level 2: Bollywood Classics

        1. question:"Sholay's popular Dialogue was: Kutte kamine, main tera________pi   jaunga. ",
           answer:"Khoon"
    

        2. question:'Which actor played the character"Babu Moshai" in Anand? ',
           answer:"Rajesh Khanna"
      

        3. question: 'Rajkumar popular dialogue in the movie Pakiza: "Apne______zamin pe mat rakhna, maile ho jayenge" ',
           answer:"Pair"
      

        4. question:"What was the name of Waheeda Rehman's character in Guide? ",
           answer:"Rosy"
      

        5. question:'Who played "Anarkali" in Mughal-e-Azam? ',
           answer:"Madhubala"
      


